[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At how many approximate degrees does Venus appear from the sun?", "correct_answer": "46", "incorrect_answers": ["78", "35", "55"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was silk first produced?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Iran", "Japan", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the movie Lucky Number Slevin released to theaters?", "correct_answer": "2006", "incorrect_answers": ["2004", "2005", "2007"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what angle is the Earth tilted?", "correct_answer": "23.5 degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["90 radians", "45 radians", "45 degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the names of Vince Vaughn and Jennifer Anistons and characters on the 2006 film The Break-Up?", "correct_answer": "Gary and Brooke", "incorrect_answers": ["Graham and Gwen", "Glen and Glenda", "Greg and Gina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most likely suffix of a web page established by a Scottish company or individual?", "correct_answer": ".uk", "incorrect_answers": [".gb", ".sc", ".br"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many make up artists worked on the film Planet of the Apes?", "correct_answer": "more than 80", "incorrect_answers": ["more than 25", "more than 37", "more than 50"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The koala is the only animal species on the planet to possess this quality.", "correct_answer": "Its brain size is extremely reduced.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "It sleeps with open eyes.", "When its hungry, it starts sucking on its tail."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the 1946 horror movie The Beast With Five Fingers set?", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["Romania", "China", "Alaska"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the constellation Ursa Major commonly known as?", "correct_answer": "The Big Dipper", "incorrect_answers": ["The Great Fisherman", "The Lion", "Hercules"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At one time both Canada and Ireland were governed by people of this same name.", "correct_answer": "Mary Robinson", "incorrect_answers": ["John McKenzie", "Sarah Mosely", "Robert Hall  Briscoe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the last reported killing of a Thylacine in Australia?", "correct_answer": "1930", "incorrect_answers": ["1880", "1900", "1910"]}]